[
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 2} \\frac {x + 2} {x - 2}",
        "answer": "dne",
        "difficulty":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to \\infty} \\frac {5x} {7x^2}",
        "answer": "0",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 12} \\frac {24x} {2x^2}",
        "answer": "1",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 1} \\frac {2x + 2} {x + 1}",
        "answer": "2",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 3} 3x - 6",
        "answer": "3",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 6} \\frac {2x - 4} {2}",
        "answer": "4",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 10} \\frac {x^2} {2x}",
        "answer": "5",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 3} \\frac {5x - 15} {x - 3}",
        "answer": "5",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 3} x^2 - 2x + 3",
        "answer": "9",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 5} x^2 - 15",
        "answer": "10",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 2} 8x - 4",
        "answer": "12",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 6} \\frac {2x^2 + x} {x}",
        "answer": "13",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 3} 2x + 7",
        "answer": "13",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 2} 3x + 8",
        "answer": "14",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 5} 7x - 20",
        "answer": "15",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 3} \\frac {12x + 9} {3}",
        "answer": "15",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 4} 6x - 7",
        "answer": "17",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 1} 10x^2 + 7x",
        "answer": "17",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to \\infty} -\\frac {x^2} {x}",
        "answer": "-inf",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to -\\infty} \\frac {3x^2 + 6x} {3x}",
        "answer": "-inf",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to \\infty} \\frac {2x^2} {x}",
        "answer": "inf",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to -\\infty} \\frac {x^2} {-x}",
        "answer": "inf",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 2} \\frac {x^2 - 4} {x - 2}",
        "answer": "4",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 3} \\frac {2x^2 + 6x} {x + 3}",
        "answer": "6",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 3} \\frac {x^2 + x - 12} {x - 3}",
        "answer": "7",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 6} \\frac {x^2 + 5x + 6} {x + 3}",
        "answer": "8",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 2} \\frac {10x^2 + 2x} {2x}",
        "answer": "11",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 6} \\frac {x^2 + 12x + 36} {x + 6}",
        "answer": "12",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 5} \\frac {3x^2 + 6x} {x + 2}",
        "answer": "15",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 20} \\frac {x^2 - 9} {x + 3}",
        "answer": "17",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 3} \\frac {4x^2(x - 5)} {2x - 10}",
        "answer": "18",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to \\infty} \\frac {2 - 4x^3 - x^2} {3x^3 - 5x}",
        "answer": "-inf",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to \\infty} \\frac {5x^2 + 4x} {2x}",
        "answer": "inf",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 4} \\frac {(2x^2 - 18)(x + 3)} {2x^2 + 12x + 18}",
        "answer": "1",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 4} \\frac {(x^2 - 2x + 1)(x + 1)} {x^2 - 1}",
        "answer": "3",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 1} \\frac {4x^2 - 8x} {2x^2 - 3x - 2}",
        "answer": "4",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 3} \\frac {3(x^2 + 6x + 9)} {3x + 9}",
        "answer": "6",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 6} \\frac {x^2 - 16} {x^2 - 8x + 16}",
        "answer": "5",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 5} \\frac {2x^2 + x - 1} {x + 1}",
        "answer": "9",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 13} \\frac {(x^2 + e^{x - 1}x)(x + 1)} {x^2 + 2x + 1}",
        "answer": "13",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 7} \\frac {(2x^2 + 3x + 1) - (x + 1)} {x + 1}",
        "answer": "14",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to 12} \\frac {5x^2 + 50x + 125} {5x + 25}",
        "answer": "17",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to -\\infty} \\frac {(x^2 + 1)(x - 1)} {x^2 - 1}",
        "answer": "-inf",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\lim_{x \\to -\\infty} \\frac {x^2 + 1} {3 - x}",
        "answer": "inf",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {Is } 4x - 9 \\text { continuous at } x = 12",
        "answer": "continuous",
        "difficulty":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {Is } x^2 + 3x - 5 \\text { continuous at } (4, 5)",
        "answer": "continuous",
        "difficulty":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {Is } \\frac {3x + 3} {3x} \\text { continuous at } [0, 1)",
        "answer": "discontinuous",
        "difficulty":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {Is } \\frac {x + 1} {x - 2} \\text { continuous at }(0, 5]",
        "answer": "discontinuous",
        "difficulty":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {Is } \\frac {5x + 2} {x^2 + 1} \\text { continuous at } x = 0",
        "answer": "continuous",
        "difficulty":"Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {Is } \\frac {2x^2 - 8x + 8} {2x - 4} \\text { continuous at } x = 2",
        "answer": "discontinuous",
        "difficulty":"Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {Is } \\frac {x^2 + 3} {\\sqrt {x + 3}} \\text { continuous at }  (-3, 3]",
        "answer": "continuous",
        "difficulty":"Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {Is } \\frac {\\sqrt {x - 2}} {x - 5} \\text { continuous at } [2, 6)",
        "answer": "discontinuous",
        "difficulty":"Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (\\frac {x^2 + x} {x^2}) \\vert_{x = 0}",
        "answer": "dne",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x^2 - 10x) \\vert_{x = 5}",
        "answer": "0",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x + 14) \\vert_{x = 7}",
        "answer": "1",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (2x) \\vert_{x = 0}",
        "answer": "2",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (3x- 4) \\vert_{x = 23}",
        "answer": "3",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (20\\ln x) \\vert_{x = 5}",
        "answer": "4",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x^2) \\vert_{x = 3}",
        "answer": "6",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d^2} {dx^2} (3x^2) \\vert_{x = 5}",
        "answer": "6",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x^2 - x + 9) \\vert_{x = 4}",
        "answer": "7",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x^2 + x) \\vert_{x = 3}",
        "answer": "7",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (2x^4) \\vert_{x = 1}",
        "answer": "8",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d^2} {dx^2} (4x^2 + 13x) \\vert_{x = 8}",
        "answer": "8",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (3x^3) \\vert_{x = 1}",
        "answer": "9",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (\\frac {5x^2} {10}) \\vert_{x = 10}",
        "answer": "10",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (33\\ln x) \\vert_{x = 3}",
        "answer": "11",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x^2 + x) \\vert_{x = 5}",
        "answer": "11",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (24\\ln x) \\vert_{x = 2}",
        "answer": "12",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x^2) \\vert_{x = 7}",
        "answer": "14",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (\\frac {x^3} {3}) \\vert_{x = 4}",
        "answer": "16",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x^2 - 16) \\vert_{x = 8}",
        "answer": "16",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (2x^3 - 6x) \\vert_{x = 2}",
        "answer": "18",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d^2} {dx^2} (x^3) \\vert_{x = 3}",
        "answer": "18",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (4x^2 + 2\\sqrt x) \\vert_{x = 2}",
        "answer": "dne",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d^2} {dx^2} (x^3 + 3x^2) \\vert_{x = -1}",
        "answer": "0",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (-\\frac {32} {x^2}) \\vert_{x = 4}",
        "answer": "1",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (8\\sqrt x) \\vert_{x = 4}",
        "answer": "2",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (\\frac {2\\sqrt {x^3}} {3}) \\vert_{x = 9}",
        "answer": "3",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (\\cos x + 6x) \\vert_{x = \\frac {\\pi} {2}}",
        "answer": "5",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (\\frac {x^3 + x^2 + 3x} {4]) \\vert_{x = 3}",
        "answer": "9",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (\\frac {6x^2} {3x} + \\frac {x^4} {4}) \\vert_{x = 2}",
        "answer": "10",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (\\sin x - x^2 + 12x) \\vert_{x = 0}",
        "answer": "13",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x^3 - x^2) \\vert_{x = 2}",
        "answer": "14",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x^2 + \\tan \\pi) \\vert_{x = 8}",
        "answer": "16",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (3x^4\\ln x) \\vert_{x = 0}",
        "answer": "dne",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x^2 - 3x)^2 \\vert_{x = 3}",
        "answer": "0",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d^2} {dx^2} (\\frac {1} {12} (x^4 + 2x^3)) \\vert_{x = 1}",
        "answer": "2",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d^3} {dx^3} (\\frac {1} {3} (x^4 - \\frac {x^3} {2}) \\vert_{x = 1}",
        "answer": "7",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (2x + 1)^2 \\vert_{x = 1}",
        "answer": "8",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} ((x - 3)^3 - 2x) \\vert_{x = 5}",
        "answer": "10",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} ((x + 1)^3 - \\frac {1} {5} x^5) \\vert_{x = 2}",
        "answer": "11",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (x^2 - 7x + 18\\sqrt x) \\vert_{x = 9}",
        "answer": "12",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d^2} {dx^2} (x^4 - 5x^3 - \\frac {x^3} {6}) \\vert_{x = 3}",
        "answer": "15",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (\\frac {(x^2 - 16)(x^4 + 4x^3)} {(3x - 12)(x^2 + 8x + 16)}) \\vert_{x = 4}",
        "answer": "16",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\displaystyle\\frac {d} {dx} (\\frac {2x^4 + 18x^3} {3x + 9}) \\vert_{x = 3}",
        "answer": "18",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {What is brown and sticky?}",
        "answer": "skull",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {Who asked?}",
        "answer": "skull",
        "difficulty": "Easy"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {If you performed an organ transplant one by one for every organ, are you still the same person?}",
        "answer": "skull",
        "difficulty": "Medium"
    },
    {
        "question": "\\text {If a tree falls in a forest, and no one is there to hear it, does it actually make a sound?}",
        "answer": "skull",
        "difficulty": "Hard"
    }
]
